Guide to the David L. Call papers, 1977-1995.
Call, David L. papers, 1977-1995
- Kellogg Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- L (General Correspondence), 1985 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Landscape Architecture, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Landscape Architecture, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Landscape Architecture, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Legislative (Governor), 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Long Island Horticultural Research Laboratory, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Long Island Horticultural Research Laboratory, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- M (General Correspondence), 1982-1985 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- M (General Correspondence), 1982-1985 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Mann Library, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Media Services, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Microbiology, Dept. of, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Migrants, 1984-1987 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Migrants, 1984-1987 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Minority Affairs, 1976-1985 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- Minorities--African, 1981-1986 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- Minorities--American Indian (American Indian Program), 1985 (Box 24, Folder 43)
- Minorities--American Indian (American Indian Program), 1985 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Minorities--American Indian (American Indian Program), 1985 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- N (General Correspondence), 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 46)
- Natural Resources, Dept. of, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 47)
- Nesheim, Malden--Reappointment (Division of Nutritional Sciences), 1984 (Box 24, Folder 48)
- Northeast Cooperative Council, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 49)
- Northeast Regional Center forRural Development, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 50)
- Northern New York Agricultural Development Program (NNYADP), 1985 (Box 24, Folder 51)
- NNYADP--Willsboro Farm & Regional Soils & Crops Program (Dean Call/R. Lucey), 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 52)
- Nutritional Sciences, Division of, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Nutritional Sciences, Division of, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Nutritional Sciences, Division of, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- NY Farm Bureau, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- NY Farm Net, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- NYS Agriculture & Markets, Dept. of, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- NYS Agriculture & Markets, Dept. of, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- NYS Assembly, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- NYS Soil & Conservation Service, 1982-1985 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- O (General Correspondence), 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Ornithology, Laboratory of (photo enclosed), 1964-1985 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Ornithology, Laboratory of, 1964-1985 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Ornithology, Laboratory of, 1964-1985 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Personal Enterprise & Small Business (Sam Seltzer), 1985 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Personal Enterprise & Small Business (Sam Seltzer), 1985 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Personal Enterprise & Small Business (Sam Seltzer), 1985 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Personal Enterprise & Small Business (Sam Seltzer), 1985 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Plans & Goals, 1972-1987 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Plant Breeding, Dept. of, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Plant Pathology, Dept. of, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Pomology, Dept. of, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Planning / Budgeting Prioritites Group, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Posner, Victor & Tracy (Donor), 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Poultry, Dept. of, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Project Ezra, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Provost Robert Barker, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Provost Robert Barker, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Provost Robert Barker, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Provost William Kennedy, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Provost William Kennedy, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- R (General Correspondence), 1982-1985 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Real Estate, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Real Estate, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Research, Office of, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Research, Office of, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Research, Office of, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Research, Office of, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Research, Office of, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Research, Office of, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Research, Office of, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Research, Office of, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 43)
- Research, Office of (Norm Scott, Director), 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- Research & Advanced Studies (Joseph Ballantyne, Vice President), 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 45)
- Residency Status for Students, 1968-1984 (Box 25, Folder 46)
- Rhodes, Frank--President, CU, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 47)
- Rhodes, Frank--President, CU, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 48)
- Robison Committee, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 49)
- Rural Schools Program, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Rural Schools Program, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Rural Schools Program, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Rural Sociology, Dept. of, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- S (General Correspondence), 1982-1985 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Sea Grant Institute, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Seneca Foods--(D.E.C. problem), 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Sponsored Programs, Office of (Thomas Rogers), 1981-1985 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- SUNY--Academic Programs, Policy & Planning, Vice Chancellor for (Sherry Penney), 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- SUNY--Academic Programs, Policy & Planning, Vice Chancellor for (Sherry Penney), 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- SUNY--Academic Programs, Policy & Planning, Vice Chancellor for (Sherry Penney), 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- SUNY--Academic Programs, Policy & Planning, Vice Chancellor for (Sherry Penney), 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- SUNY--Chancellor, Office of the (Clifton Wharton), 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- SUNY--Chancellor, Office of the (Clifton Wharton), 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- SUNY--Chancellor, Office of the (Clifton Wharton), 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- SUNY--Chancellor, Office of the (Clifton Wharton), 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- SUNY--Research, Graduate Studies & Professional Programs, Vice Chancellor for (Alden Haffner), 1984 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- SUNY--Research, Graduate Studies & Professional Programs, Vice Chancellor for (Alden Haffner), 1984 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Swedish University ofAgricultural Sciences, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- T (General Correspondence), 1982-1985 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Title XII, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Tropical Studies, Organization of, 1982-1985 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Uihlein, Henry (Donor), 1985 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- University Relations, Vice President for (John Burness), 1985 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- University Unions, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Urban Horticulture Institute, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- V (General Correspondence), 1982-1985 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Vegetable Crops, Dept. of, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Vice Presidency of Dean Call, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Vice Presidency of Dean Call, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Vice Provost Barry Adams, 1984-1987 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Vice Provost J.W. Spencer, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- Vice Provost J.W. Spencer, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- Vice Provost J.W. Spencer, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- Vice Provost J.W. Spencer, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- Vice Provost J.W. Spencer, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- W (General Correspondence), 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- Washington Symposium, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- Wing, Kenneth (Associate Dean, CALS), 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- Academic Computing Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- Academic Computing Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- Academic Computing Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- Academic Computing Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 48)
- Academic Computing Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 49)
- Administrative Services (Robert Young), 1986 (Box 26, Folder 50)
- Administrative Services, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 51)
- Administrative Services, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 52)
- Administrative Services, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 53)
- Adirondack Park Research, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Adirondack Park Research, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Admissions, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Admissions & Financial Aid (Susan Murphy, Dean), 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- African Development Initiative, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- African Development Initiative, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- African Development Initiative, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Agricultural Engineering, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Agricultural Engineering, Dept of, 1984-1986 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Agricultural Information Systems Committee, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Agricultural Information Systems Committee, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Agricultural Organizations, Council of, 1984-1986 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Agriculture, Advisory Council on, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Agriculture, Advisory Council on, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Agriculture in the Classroom, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Agriculture Student Positive Action Council (AgPAC), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Agronomy, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Agronomy, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Agronomy, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Agway, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Alar-85 (Plant Growth Regulant), 1986 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Alpha Gamma Rho Fraternity, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Alumni Affairs & Development, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Alumni Affairs & Development, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Alumni Affairs & Development, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Alumni Affairs & Development, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- American Indian Program, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- American Indian Program, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- American Indian Program, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- American Indian Program, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- American Indian Program, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- American Indian Program, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- Animal Science, Dept. of, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- Animal Science, Dept. of, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 38)
- Animal Science, Dept. of, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- Arnot Forest, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- Arts & Sciences, College of, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 41)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 42)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 43)
- Baker, E.V., 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 44)
- Baker, E.V., 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 45)
- Biochemistry, Molecular & Cell Biology, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 46)
- Biological Sciences, Division of, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 47)
- Biological Sciences, Division of--Research & History, 1981-1986 (Box 27, Folder 48)
- Biological Sciences, Division of--Research & History, 1981-1986 (Box 27, Folder 49)
- Biometrics, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 50)
- Biotechnology Institute, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 51)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1984-1987 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1984-1987 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1984-1987 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1984-1987 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1984-1987 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Budget, Office of, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- C (General Correspondence), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Campus Affairs (William Gurowitz, Vice President), 1984-1987 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Career Development, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Carnation Project, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Carver, Roy J. Trust, 1981-1988 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Chemicals/Pesticides Program, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- China, 1981-1984 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- China--Nanjing, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- CISER (Cornell Institute for Social & Economic Research), 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- CISER (Cornell Institute for Social & Economic Research), 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- CISER (Cornell Institute for Social & Economic Research), 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Cohn Farm, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Cohn Farm, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Cohn Foundation, 1984-1989 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Commencement Office, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Commencement Office, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Communication Arts, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Communication Arts, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Computers, 1985-1988 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Congress Members, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Controller, Office of the, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Cooperative Extension, 1984-1986 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Cooperative Extension, 1984-1986 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Cooperative Extension, 1984-1986 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Cooperative Extension, 1984-1986 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Cooperative Extension Commission, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- Cooperative Extension Commission, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Cornell Abroad, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Cornell Abroad, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- Cornell Abroad, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- Cornell Laboratory for Environmental Applications of Remote Sensing (CLEARS), 1984-1986 (Box 28, Folder 37)
- Cornell Laboratory for Environmental Applications of Remote Sensing (CLEARS), 1984-1986 (Box 28, Folder 38)
- Cornell Plantations, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 39)
- Cornell Plantations, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 40)
- Corporate Development & Foundation Relations, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 41)
- County Agents, 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 42)
- Cuba Cheese, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 43)
- D (General Correspondence), 1984-1987 (Box 28, Folder 44)
- Dean's Council, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 45)
- Dean's Council, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 46)
- Dean's Statutory Meeting, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 47)
- Dean's Statutory Meeting, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 48)
- E (General Correspondence), 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Ecology & Systematics, Section of, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Education, NYS Dept. of, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Education, NYS Dept. of, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Education, Dept. of (Dalva Hedlund), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Education, Dept. of (Dalva Hedlund), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Education, Dept. of (Dalva Hedlund), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Egner, John (Associate Provost), 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Empire Farm Days, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Empire State Food & Agricultural Leadership Institute, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Empire State Food & Agricultural Leadership Institute, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Empire State Food & Agricultural Leadership Institute, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Empire State Food & Agricultural Leadership Institute, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Empire State Food & Agricultural Leadership Institute, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Engineering, College of, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Engineering, College of, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Entomology, Dept. of, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Entomology, Dept. of, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Entrepreneur of the Year Award, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Equalization & Assessment, Division of, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Equalization & Assessment, Division of, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- F (General Correspondence), 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Faculty--Agriculture, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Faculty--Agriculture, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Faculty--Agriculture, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Faculty--Reception for New, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Faculty--University, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Faculty--University, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Farm Credit Banks of Springfield, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- Farming Alternatives Project, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- Finance & Business Office, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- Finance & Business Office, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 39)
- Financial Aid, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 40)
- Fish & Wildlife Cooperative Units, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 41)
- Fish & Wildlife Cooperative Units, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 42)
- Fish & Wildlife Management Board, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 43)
- Floriculture & Ornamental Horticulture, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 44)
- Floriculture & Ornamental Horticulture, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 45)
- Food & Agricultural Sciences, Joint Council on, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Food Processing & Development Laboratory, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Food Science, Institute of, 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Food Science, Institute of, 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Forensics, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- G (General Correspondence), 1986 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Gamma Sigma Delta (Honor Society of Agriculture), 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- General Foods World Food Prize, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- General Foods World Food Prize, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- General Foods World Food Prize, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- General Foods World Food Prize, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- General Foods World Food Prize, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- General Foods World Food Prize, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Genetics & Development, Section of, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Gifts--Committee on Acquisition & Use, 1978-1987 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Global Change, Proposed Center for (Carl Sagan), 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Government Affairs, Office of, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Government Affairs, Office of, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Government Affairs, Office of, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Government Affairs, Office of (Robert Barlow), 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Governor (Mario Cuomo), 1987 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Graduate School, 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Grape & Wine Industry, 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- H (General Correspondence), 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Hatfield Fellows, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Human Ecology, College of, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Human Ecology, College of, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- IAD (International Agriculture) Steering Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- IAD (International Agriculture) Steering Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- ICET (Institute for Comparative & Environmental Toxicology), 1987 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Industrial Innovation Extension Service, Program for, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Industrial Innovation Extension Service, Program for, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Industrial Innovation Extension Service, Program for, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Industrial Innovation Extension Service, Program for, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Industrial Innovation Extension Service, Program for, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 35)
- Industrial Innovation Extension Service, Program for, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 36)
- Industrial & Labor Relations (I & LR), 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- Information Technologies, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 38)
- Instruction, Office of, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 39)
- Instruction, Office of, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 40)
- Instruction, Office of, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 41)
- Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 42)
- Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 43)
- Intern Program, 1981-1987 (Box 30, Folder 44)
- International Agriculture, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 45)
- International Agriculture, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 46)
- International Studies, Center for, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 47)
- International Studies, Center for, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 48)
- J (General Correspondence), 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Johnson Graduate School of Management, 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- K (Correspondence), 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Kellogg Foundation, 1981-1987 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- L (General Correspondence), 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Landscape Architecture, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Landscape Architecture, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Libraries, 1981-1987 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Life Safety, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Long Island Horticultural Research Laboratory, 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- M (General Correspondence), 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Mann Library, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Mann Library, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Media Services, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Media Services, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Microbiology, Dept. of, 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Microbiology Committee, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Microbiology Committee, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Minorities (Henry Louis Gates, Jr. & Walter Cohen), 1987 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Minorities--Asians, 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Minority Education Council, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- N (General Correspondence), 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Natural Resources, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Natural Resources, Dept. of, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Neurobiology & Behavior, Section of, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Northeast Cooperative Council, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Northeast Dairy Foods Research Center (Dave Barbano, Director), 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- Northeast Dairy Foods Research Center (Dave Barbano, Director), 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 28)
- Northeast Dairy Foods Research Center (Dave Barbano, Director), 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 29)
- Northeast Regional Center for Rural Development, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 30)
- Northern New York Agricultural Development Program, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- Nutritional Sciences, Division of, 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- NY Farm Bureau, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 33)
- NY Farm Bureau, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 34)
- NY Farm Net, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- NY Farm Net, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 36)
- NY Farm Net, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 37)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 38)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 39)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 40)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 41)
- NYS Agriculture & Markets, Dept, of, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 42)
- NYS Agriculture & Markets, Dept, of, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 43)
- NYS Agriculture & Markets, Dept, of, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 44)
- NYS Agriculture & Markets, Dept, of, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 45)
- NYS Assembly, 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 46)
- NYS Environmental Conservation, Dept. of, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 47)
- NYS Fair, 1984-1988 (Box 31, Folder 48)
- NYS Soil & Water Conservation Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 49)
- NYS Soil & Water Conservation Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 50)
- NYS Soil & Water Conservation Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 51)
- NYS Soil & Water Conservation Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 52)
- O (General Correspondence), 1985-1987 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Ornithology Laboratory, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Ornithology Laboratory, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Ornithology Laboratory, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- P (General Correspondence), 1985-1987 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- P (General Correspondence), 1985-1987 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- PACNYS (Professional Agricultural Consultants of New York State), 1984-1987 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Personal Enterprise & Small Business Management Program, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 8)